Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, 1907-1952; Series 2; 47 microfilm reels
  - Local unions correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Local #528, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 27)
    - Local #529, Elmira, New York, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 28)
    - Local #530, Fond du Lac, Wisconsin, 1943-1948 •; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 29)
    - Local #530, Toledo, Ohio, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 30)
    - Local #531, Wisconsin Rapids, Wisconsin, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 31)
    - Local #532, Springfield, Illinois, 1940-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 32)
    - Local #532, Springfield, Illinois, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 1)
    - Local #533, Reno, Nevada, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 2)
    - Local #534, Sedalia, Missouri, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 3)
    - Local #535, Coffeyville, Kansas, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 4)
    - Local #535, Dallas, Texas, 1947-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 5)
    - Local #535, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 6)
    - Local #536, Hartford, Connecticut, 1945-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 7)
    - Local #537, Denver, Colorado, 1942-1944, 1948, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 8)
    - Local #538, Kittanning, Pennsylvania, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 9)
    - Local #539, San Francisco, California, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 10)
    - Local #539, Winchester, Virginia, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 11)
    - Local #540, Syracuse, New York, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 12)
    - Local #541, Kansas City, Missouri, 1941-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 13)
    - Local #541, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 14)
    - Local #541, Kansas City, Missouri, 1947-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 15)
    - Local #541, Kansas City, Missouri, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 16)
    - Local #541, Kansas City, Missouri, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 17)
    - Local #542, San Diego, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 15a)
      In the original paper finding aid this is a second folder 15 on reel 33. For digital object identification this segment is designated 15a.
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1941; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 16a)
      In the original paper finding aid this is a second folder 16 on reel 33. For digital object identification this segment is designated 16a.
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 17a)
      In the original paper finding aid this is a second folder 17 on reel 33. For digital object identification this segment is designated 17a.
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 18)
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 19)
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1945-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 20)
    - Local #543, Lafayette, Indiana, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 33, Segment 21)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1939-1941; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 1)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 2)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 3)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 4)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 5)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 6)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 7)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 8)
    - Local #544, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 9)
    - Local #545, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 10)
    - Local #546, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 11)
    - Local #547, Los Angeles, California, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 12)
    - Local #548, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 13)
    - Local #549, Minerva, Ohio, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 14)
    - Local #549, Kingsport, Tennessee, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 15)
    - Local #550, New York, New York, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 16)
    - Local #551, Wallace, Idaho, 1942, 1944, 1947, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 17)
    - Local #552, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1942, 1944, 1947 -1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 18)
    - Local #552, Kansas City, Missouri, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 19)
    - Local #553, New York, New York, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 20)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1938, 1942- -1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 21)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 22)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 23)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 34, Segment 24)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 1)
    - Local #554, Omaha, Nebraska, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 2)
    - Local #555, Cleveland, Ohio, 1943, 1946- -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 3)
    - Local #556, Pasco & Walla Walla, Washington, 1947-1949, n.d.; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 4)
    - Local #557, Baltimore, Maryland, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 5)
    - Local #557, Baltimore, Maryland, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 6)
    - Local #558, Buffalo, New York, 1941-1943, 1946- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 7)
    - Local #559, Hartford, Connecticut, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 8)
    - Local #559, Hartford, Connecticut, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 9)
    - Local #559, Hartford, Connecticut, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 10)
    - Local #560, Hoboken, New Jersey, 1917, 1942- • 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 11)
    - skipped, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 12)
    - Local #559, Hartford, Connecticut, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 13)
    - Local #561, Cleveland, Ohio, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 14)
    - Local #562, DeKalb, Illinois, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 15)
    - Local #563, Menasha, Wisconsin, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 16)
    - Local #564, Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 17)
    - Local #564, Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1947-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 18)
    - Local #564, Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 19)
    - Local #564, Meadville, Pennsylvania, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 20)
    - Local #565, Waco, Texas, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 21)
    - Local #566, Seattle, Washington, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 22)
    - Local #567, Tacoma, Washington, 1941, 1946, 1949- -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 23)
    - Local #568, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 24)
    - Local #568, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 25)
    - Local #569, Astoria, Oregon, 1939, 1944- 1945, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 26)
    - Local #570, Baltimore, Maryland, 1941, 1947- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 35, Segment 27)
    - Local #571, Elyria, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 1)
    - Local #572, Long Beach, California, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 2)
    - Local #573, Boston, Massachusetts, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 3)
    - Local #574, Cape Girardeau, Missouri, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 4)
    - Local #575, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1943-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 5)
    - Local #576, New Athens, Illinois, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 6)
    - Local #576, San Jose, California, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 7)
    - Local #577, Amarillo, Texas, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 8)
    - Local #578, Carlyle, Illinois, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 9)
    - Local #578, Los Angeles, California, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 10)
    - Local #579, Janesville, Wisconsin, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 11)
    - Local #580, Lansing, Michigan, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 12)
    - Local #581, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 13)
    - Local #581, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 14)
    - Local #582, Evansville, Indiana, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 15)
    - Local #583, Abilene, Texas, 1944-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 16)
    - Local #583, Abilene, Texas, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 17)
    - Local #584, New York, New York, 1920-1922, 1942- • 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 18)
    - Local #584, New York, New York, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 19)
    - Local #585, Washington, Pennsylvania, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 20)
    - Local #586, Kansas City, Missouri, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 21)
    - Local #587, Kansas City, Missouri, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 22)
    - Local #588, Oakland, California, 1942, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 23)
    - Local #589, Port Angeles, Washington, 1939, 1943, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 24)
    - Local #590, Vineland, New Jersey, 1935, 1942- -1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 25)
    - Local #590, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 26)
    - Local #590, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 27)
    - Local #591, Meridian and Tupelo, Mississippi, 1942, 1944- -1951 i; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 28)
    - Local #592, Richmond, Virginia, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 29)
    - Local #592, Richmond, Virginia, 1946-1952, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 30)
    - Local #593, Kalispell, Montana, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 36, Segment 31)
    - Local #594, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1942-1945, 1948- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 1)
    - Local #595, Los Angeles, California, 1942, 1945- -1947, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 2)
    - Local #596, Anna, Illinois, 1943-1951, n.d.; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 3)
    - Local #597, Barre, Vermont, 1942-1952 1927; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 4)
    - Local #598, Los Angeles, California, 1942, 1944- -1947, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 5)
    - Local #599, Sullivan, Indiana, 1926; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 6)
    - Local #599, Tacoma, Washington, 1944, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 7)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1916-1917, 1920- 1922,1930, 1932, 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 8)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1940-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 9)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1943-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 10)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 11)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 12)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 13)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 14)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 15)
    - Local #600, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1952 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 16)
    - Local #601, Stockton, California, 1946, 1948- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 17)
    - Local #602, Houston, Texas, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 18)
    - Local #602, New York, New York, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 19)
    - Local #603, St, Louis, Missouri, 1915-1917, 1933-1934, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 20)
    - Local #604, St. Louis, Missouri, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 21)
    - Local #604, St. Louis, Missouri, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 22)
    - Local #605, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1910, 1911; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 23)
    - Local #605, Washington, D.C., 1943, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 24)
    - Local #606, St. Louis, Missouri, 1914, 1925, 1932, 1946, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 25)
    - Local #607, St. Louis, Missouri, 1914; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 26)
    - Local #607, New York, New York, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 27)
    - Local #608, St. Louis, Missouri, 1920; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 28)
    - Local #608, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 29)
    - Local #609, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1936, 1942, 1944 -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 30)
    - Local #610, Oakland, California, 1933, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 31)
    - Local #611, St. Louis, Missouri, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 32)
    - Local #611, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 33)
    - Local #611, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 34)
    - Local #612, Birmingham, Alabama, 1941-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 35)
    - Local #612, Birmingham, Alabama, 1943-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 37, Segment 36)
    - Local #612, Birmingham, Alabama, 1945-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 1)
    - Local #612, Birmingham, Alabama, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 2)
    - Local #613, Jacksonville, Florida, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 2a)
      In the original paper finding aid this is a second folder 2 on reel 38. For digital object identification this segment is designated 2a.
    - Local #613, Jacksonville, Florida, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 3)
    - Local #613, Jacksonville, Florida, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 4)
    - Local #614, Pontiac, Michigan, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 5)
    - Local #614, Pontiac, Michigan, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 6)
    - Local #615, Virginia, Minnesota, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 7)
    - Local #616, Fresno, California, 1946-1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 8)
    - Local #617, Dumont, New Jersey, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 9)
    - Local #618, St. Louis, Missouri, 1941-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 10)
    - Local #618, St. Louis, Missouri, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 11)
    - Local #618, St. Louis, Missouri, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 12)
    - Local #618, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 13)
    - Local #619, Manitowoc, Wisconsin, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 14)
    - Local #620, Sunbury, Pennsylvania, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 15)
    - Local #620, Salina, Kansas, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 16)
    - Local #621, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 17)
    - Local #621, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 18)
    - Local #621, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1947-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 19)
    - Local #621, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 20)
    - Local #622, Baltimore, Maryland, 1943, 1948, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 21)
    - Local #623, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1932, 1934, 1943- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 22)
    - Local #624, San Rafael, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 38, Segment 23)
    - Local #625, Fremont, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 1)
    - Local #626, Los Angeles, California, 1942, 1944, 1948- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 2)
    - Local #627, Peoria, Illinois, 1941-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 3)
    - Local #627, Peoria, Illinois, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 4)
    - Local #628, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1945-1946, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 5)
    - Local #629, Oakland, California, 1945, 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 6)
    - Local #630, Los Angeles, California, 1941, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 7)
    - Local #631, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 8)
    - Local #632, Marion, Ohio, 1939, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 9)
    - Local #632, St. Louis, Missouri, 1947, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 10)
    - Local #633, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 11)
    - Local #633, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 12)
    - Local #634, Hillsboro, Oregon, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 13)
    - Local #635, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 14)
    - Local #635, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 15)
    - Local #636, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1941-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 16)
    - Local #636, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 17)
    - Local #636, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 18)
    - Local #636, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 19)
    - Local #637, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1910; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 20)
    - Local #637, Zanesville, Ohio, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 21)
    - Local #637, Zanesville, Ohio, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 22)
    - Local #637, Zanesville, Ohio, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 23)
    - Local #638, Mascoutah, Illinois, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 24)
    - Local #638, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 39, Segment 25)
    - Local #639, Washington, D.C., 1938, 1940-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 1)
    - Local #639, Washington, D.C., 1939-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 2)
    - Local #640, Los Angeles, California, 1942-1945, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 3)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 4)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 5)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 6)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 7)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 8)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 9)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 10)
    - Local #641, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 11)
    - skipped, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 12)
    - Local #642, Faribault, Minnesota, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 13)
    - Local #643, New York, New York, , 1943, 1945- -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 14)
    - Local #644, Princeton, Indiana, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 15)
    - Local #645, Rochester, New York, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 16)
    - Local #646, Boston, Massachusetts, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 17)
    - Local #647, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1942-1947, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 18)
    - Local #648, Alexandria, Virginia, 1935; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 19)
    - Local #648, Plattsburg, New York, 1942, 1946- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 20)
    - Local #649, St. Louis, Missouri, 1918, 1920; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 21)
    - Local #649, Jamestown, New York, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 22)
    - Local #650, Waterloo, Iowa, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 23)
    - Local #651, Eldorado, Illinois, 1931; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 24)
    - Local #651, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 25)
    - Local #652, Corpus Christi, Texas, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 26)
    - Local #653, Brockton, Massachusetts, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 27)
    - Local #654, New York, New York, 1915; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 28)
    - Local #654, Springfield, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 29)
    - Local #655, Mt. Carmel, Illinois, 1944, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 30)
    - Local #655, San Mateo County, California, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 31)
    - Local #656, Eugene, Oregon, 1945-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 32)
    - Local #657, San Antonio, Texas, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 33)
    - Local #657, San Antonio, Texas, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 40, Segment 34)
    - Local #658, St. Louis, Missouri, 1925, 1942- 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 1)
    - Local #659, Piano, Illinois, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 2)
    - Local #659, Rome, Georgia, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 3)
    - Local #659, Omaha, Nebraska, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 4)
    - Local #660, Peoria, Illinois, 1944-1947, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 5)
    - Local #661, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 6)
    - Local #661, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1947-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 7)
    - Local #661, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 8)
    - Local #661, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 9)
    - Local #662, Eau Claire, Wisconsin, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 10)
    - Local #662, Eau Claire, Wisconsin, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 11)
    - Local #663, Detroit, Michigan, 1926, 1948- -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 12)
    - Local #664, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 13)
    - Local #665, San Francisco, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 41, Segment 14)